{
    "subject": "Ward_Kimball",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "Man_in_Space",
    "human_readable": "Ward Kimball created the film Man in Space.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8653194904327393,
            "question": "Who created the film Man in Space?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8335918188095093,
            "question": "What is the name of the film created by Ward Kimball?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6350350379943848,
            "question": "What other works did Ward Kimball create?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6208930611610413,
            "question": "Was the film Man in Space a success?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5666841268539429,
            "question": "What techniques were used in the film Man in Space?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.500205397605896,
            "question": "How did the film Man in Space influence later films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4378315806388855,
            "question": "Were there any sequels or related films to Man in Space?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42211097478866577,
            "question": "What genre is the film Man in Space likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4059011936187744,
            "question": "When was the film Man in Space most likely made?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.339728444814682,
            "question": "Did the film Man in Space win any awards?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ward Kimball created the film Man in Space.",
            "html": "yago_2878_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was the film Man in Space most likely made?",
            "html": "yago_2878_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film Man in Space likely to be?",
            "html": "yago_2878_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were there any sequels or related films to Man in Space?",
            "html": "yago_2878_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_2878_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_2878_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_2878_119.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_2878_141.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_2878_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_2878_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_2878_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_2878_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_2878_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_2878_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Ward Kimball and his role in creating the film \"Man in Space.\" For example, from `139.txt` and `135.txt`, it is stated that \"Man in Space\" was directed by Ward Kimball and premiered on March 9, 1955. Therefore, the statement that Ward Kimball created the film \"Man in Space\" is supported by the documents provided."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}